A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Foundation of the Asia-Pacific Human Rights Information Center (09850909), 1998 April 17-1999 April 16 (Reel 8336)
    SUPPORT FOR SOUTH ASIAN WORKSHOP ON HUMAN RIGHTS EDUCATION IN SCHOOLS
    South Asia; Foundation of the Asia-Pacific Human Rights Information Center
  - Foundation of the International Academy of the Environment (09350204), 1992 December 01-1993 February 28 (Reel 6571)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR AN INTERNATIONAL MEETING ON ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY RESEARCH (021)
    Global; Foundation of the International Academy of the Environment
  - Foundation of The Netherlands Economic Institute (06200018), 1961 November 07-1962 November 06 (Reel 0757)
    STUDY OF THE FINANCING OF AFRICAN HIGHER EDUCATION
    $40,000.00;$36,397.96
    Foundation of The Netherlands Economic Institute
  - Foundation of the University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey (09000235), 1990 January 01-1991 December 31 (Reel 6324)
    SUPPORT FOR A VIDEO PACKAGE TO TRAIN TEACHERS ABOUT EXCEPTIONAL DEVELOPMENT IN YOUNG CHILDREN FROM LOW-INCOME FAMILIES
    United States; New Jersey; Foundation of the University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey
  - Foundation Points of Encounter for Changes in Daily Life (09950778), 1999 January 01-2001 May 31 (Reel 8921)
    STRENGTHEN CIVIL SOCIETY'S CAPACITY TO INFLUENCE THE RECONSTRUCTION PROCESS AFTER HURRICANE MITCH IN CENTRAL AMERICA
    Brown, Kimberli R.;Barry, Deborah;Faulhaber, Ingrid S.
    Nicaragua; Central America; Natural disasters--Central America; Emergency management --Central America; Civil society -- Central America; Foundation Points of Encounter for Changes in Daily Life
  - Foundation S.p.a.c.e. (09800290), 1997 October 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9025)
    SUPPORT TO BUILD THE CAPACITY AND SUPPORT PROJECTS OF A KEY SOCIALPOLICY INSTITUTE IN SLOVAKIA
    Slovakia; Europe, Eastern; Foundation S.p.a.c.e.
  - Foundation to Aid Industrial Recovery (08000691), 1981 May 14-1987 December 31 (Reel 5924)
    EXPAND MANAGEMENT SERVICES TO AGENCIES AND ORGANIZATIONS WORKING FOR THE BENEFIT OF UNORGANIZED POOR AND DISADVANTAGED PERSONS
    $276,000.00;$276,000.00
    Conway, Gordon R.
    India; Foundation to Aid Industrial Recovery
  - Foundation to Aid Industrial Recovery (08700344), 1987 July 15-1991 July 14 (Reel 6078)
    IN-COUNTRY MANAGEMENT TRAINING FOR INDIAN NGOS AND PARASTATAL ORGANIZATIONS
    $200,000.00;$61,093.23
  - Foundation to Promote Sustainable Development (Terram) (09850917), 1998 April 01-1999 March 31 (Reel 8655)
    SUPPORT CITIZEN PARTICIPATION AND RESEARCH ON SUSTAINABLE NATIVE FOREST DEVELOPMENT IN CHILE
    Chile; Sustainable forestry--Chile--Citizen participation; Sustainable development--Chile; Foundation to Promote Sustainable Development (Terram)
  - Foundation to Promote Sustainable Development (Terram) (10000119), 1999 November 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 8962)
    SUPPORT CITIZEN PARTICIPATION TO DEFEND AND PROTECT NATIVE FORESTS THROUGH LITIGATION, APPLIED RESEARCH, COMMUNICATION ACTIVITIES IN CHILE, AND TWO REGIONAL WORKSHOPS TO SHARE LESSONS LEARNED.
    Abregú, Martín
    Argentina; Chile; Peru; Conservation of natural resources -- Chile -- Citizen participation; Sustainable development--Chile--Citizen participation; Forests and forestry -- Chile; Foundation to Promote Sustainable Development (Terram)
  - Foundation Women's Feature Service Nederland (09701942), 1997 September 01-2002 March 31 (Reel 8877)
    SUPPORT FOR WORKSHOPS ON RELIGION AND GENDER FOR JOURNALISTS, ACADEMICS AND NGO PROFESSIONALS IN THE NETHERLANDS AND INDIA
    India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delhi);Human Rights;KC & F - Office of the Vice President
    Buchanan, Constance H.;McDaniel, Jr., Joseph M.;Phillips, Barbara
    Global; Foundation Women's Feature Service Nederland
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05090002): STUDY OF AMERICAN - SOVIET RELATIONS, 1950 (Reel 0487)
    STUDY OF AMERICAN - SOVIET RELATIONS
    Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05190049): STUDY OF UNIVERSAL DISARMAMENT - GRENVILLE CLARK, 1951 (Reel 0489)
    STUDY OF UNIVERSAL DISARMAMENT - GRENVILLE CLARK
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05190050): STUDY OF INTERCULTURAL RELATIONS - REDFIELD, 1951 (Reel 0505)
    STUDY OF INTERCULTURAL RELATIONS - REDFIELD
    $83,000.00;$83,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05200071): GRANTS-IN-AID FOR PROMINENT AND PROMISING SCIENTISTS IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES, 1952 February 01-1965 December 31 (Reel 0012;0013;0014)
    GRANTS-IN-AID FOR PROMINENT AND PROMISING SCIENTISTS IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES
    $300,000.00;$293,210.05
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05200083): ITR FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - ASIA, NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST, 1952 (Reel 5847 (GAF ONLY))
    ITR FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - ASIA, NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST
    $480,000.00;$470,258.98
    Asia; South Asia; East Asia; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05290072): ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR INVENTORIES OF BEHAVIORAL KNOWLEDGE, 1952 (Reel 0005)
    ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR INVENTORIES OF BEHAVIORAL KNOWLEDGE
    $5,000.00;$512.38
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05290085): CONDITIONS OF PEACE, 1952 (Reel 0490;1192)
    CONDITIONS OF PEACE
    $50,000.00;$41,378.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05290092): ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR TRAINING AND RESEARCH PROGRAM, 1952 (Reel 5941(GAF))
    ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR TRAINING AND RESEARCH PROGRAM
    $79,307.00;$79,307.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05290129): REFUGEES - ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES, 1952 (Reel 0482)
    REFUGEES - ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES
    $58,000.00;$58,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05300009): FIRST YEAR GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS FOR THOSE WHO HAVE NOT CONCENTRATED IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES, 1953 (Reel 5113)
    FIRST YEAR GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS FOR THOSE WHO HAVE NOT CONCENTRATED IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES
    $150,000.00;$104,522.89
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05300085): NON-ACADEMIC FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST, 1953 (Reel 5282)
    NON-ACADEMIC FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Asia & The Pacific [ASIA]
    $55,675.00;$55,675.00
    Middle East; South Asia; East Asia; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05390010): PROGRAM FOR INTERDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH AND STUDY, 1953 (Reel 0004;3031)
    PROGRAM FOR INTERDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH AND STUDY
    $303,000.00;$303,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05390016): COMMISSION ON TELEVISION, 1953 (Reel 1032)
    COMMISSION ON TELEVISION
    $82,000.00;$82,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05390040): SELF-INQUIRY PROGRAM IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES - ADMINISTRATIVE EXPENSES, 1953 (Reel 0005)
    SELF-INQUIRY PROGRAM IN THE BEHAVIORAL SCIENCES - ADMINISTRATIVE EXPENSES
    $44,218.00;$44,218.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05390191): RESOURCES AND CONSERVATION, 1953 (Reel 0387)
    RESOURCES AND CONSERVATION
    $52,519.00;$52,519.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05390226): CONDUCT OF GOVERNMENTAL AFFAIRS, 1953 (Reel 1192)
    CONDUCT OF GOVERNMENTAL AFFAIRS
    $10,518.00;$10,518.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05400108): FOREIGN STUDY RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP PROG.-ADD. NON- ACADEMIC AWARDS FOR STUDY RE ASIA, THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST, 1954-55 (Reel 0950)
    FOREIGN STUDY & RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP PROG.-ADD. NON- ACADEMIC AWARDS FOR STUDY RE ASIA, THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST, 1954-55
    $50,000.00;$30,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05400146): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO AFRICA FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56, 1954 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO AFRICA FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56
    $200,000.00;$146,042.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490030): TV-RADIO WORKSHOP (OMNIBUS), 1954-55 (Reel 1032)
    TV-RADIO WORKSHOP (OMNIBUS), 1954-55
    $1,780,000.00;$1,779,935.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490031): STUDY OF UNIVERSAL DISARMAMENT UNDER THE DIRECTION OF GRENVILLE CLARK, 1954 (Reel 0490)
    STUDY OF UNIVERSAL DISARMAMENT UNDER THE DIRECTION OF GRENVILLE CLARK
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490067): INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF BUSINESS AND PROFESSIONAL WOMEN - SYRIA, 1954 (Reel 0421)
    INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF BUSINESS AND PROFESSIONAL WOMEN - SYRIA
    $47,500.00;$47,500.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490097): U.N. HIGH COMMISSIONER FOR REFUGEES, ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR GRANTS TO AID REFUGEES., 1954 January 01-1958 December 04 (Reel 0486)
    U.N. HIGH COMMISSIONER FOR REFUGEES, ADMINISTRATION EXPENSES FOR GRANTS TO AID REFUGEES.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490109): SHORT-TERM LOCAL CONSULTANTS AND SPECIALISTS FOR THE BURMA STATE AGRICULTURAL INSTITUTE, 1954 (Reel 0825)
    SHORT-TERM LOCAL CONSULTANTS AND SPECIALISTS FOR THE BURMA STATE AGRICULTURAL INSTITUTE
    $939,400.00;$939,400.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490110): SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS ON HEALTH EDUCATION AND SERVICES AND FEES RELATING TO SOUTHERN LANGUAGES BOOK TRUST (INDIA), 1954 January 01-1961 August 30 (Reel 0884)
    SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS ON HEALTH EDUCATION AND SERVICES AND FEES RELATING TO SOUTHERN LANGUAGES BOOK TRUST (INDIA)
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delhi)
    $1,021,926.00;$1,021,926.00
    India; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490111): EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES -INDONESIA- SPECIALISTS FOR HIGHER EDUCATION, 1954 June 30-1956 September 30 (Reel 0842)
    EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES -INDONESIA- SPECIALISTS FOR HIGHER EDUCATION
    $182,300.00;$182,300.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490112): EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES (LEBANON) - SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN RURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1953 October 01-1962 September 30 (Reel 0794;5975)
    EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES (LEBANON) - SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS IN RURAL DEVELOPMENT
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon;Lebanon
    $400,594.00;$400,594.00
    Lebanon; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490113): EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES - PAKISTAN- SPECIALISTS TRAINING WITHIN INDUSTRY, 1954 June 30-1956 September 30 (Reel 1039)
    EXPENSES OF OVERSEAS FIELD OFFICES - PAKISTAN- SPECIALISTS TRAINING WITHIN INDUSTRY
    Pakistan
    $275,500.00;$275,500.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490126): UNITED NATIONS FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION - AGRICULTURAL CREDIT CONFERENCE, 1954 (Reel 0931)
    UNITED NATIONS FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION - AGRICULTURAL CREDIT CONFERENCE
    $7,500.00;$4,054.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490133): UNITED NATIONS FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION - CENTER ON LAND PROBLEMS CONFERENCE, 1954 (Reel 0815)
    UNITED NATIONS FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION - CENTER ON LAND PROBLEMS CONFERENCE
    $25,751.00;$25,751.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05490165): SURVEY OF THE CHINESE REFUGEE SITUATION IN HONG KONG, 1954 (Reel 0486)
    SURVEY OF THE CHINESE REFUGEE SITUATION IN HONG KONG
    $50,000.00;$23,544.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500006): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56
    $500,000.00;$308,950.00
    SouthEast Asia; Foundation-Administered Project (FAP)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500007): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO SOVIET UNION AND EASTERN EUROPE FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO SOVIET UNION AND EASTERN EUROPE FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56
    $200,000.00;$188,785.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500202): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST - SPECIAL FELLOWSHIPS FOR 1955-56, 1955 September 12-1956 September 11 (Reel 0953)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST - SPECIAL FELLOWSHIPS FOR 1955-56
    $90,000.00;$56,936.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500212): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57
    $100,000.00;$63,210.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500213): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO ASIA AND THE NEAR AND MIDDLE EAST FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1955-56 (Reel 5349)
    $500,000.00;$377,544.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500214): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO AFRICA FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57, 1955 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO AFRICA FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57
    $200,000.00;$129,395.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05500215): FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO SOVIET UNION AND EASTERN EUROPE FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57, 1955 (Reel 5349)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING RELATING TO SOVIET UNION AND EASTERN EUROPE FOR THE ACADEMIC YEAR 1956-57
    $200,000.00;$156,214.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590047): INTERNATIONAL BANK FOR RECONSTRUCTION AND DEVELOPMENT - SUPPORT ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE, 1955 (Reel 0667)
    INTERNATIONAL BANK FOR RECONSTRUCTION AND DEVELOPMENT - SUPPORT ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590082): EXPENSES FOR TRAINING AND RESEARCH SPECIALIST IN THE NEAR EAST (HOWARD REED), 1955 August 15-1957 August 14 (Reel 0783)
    EXPENSES FOR TRAINING AND RESEARCH SPECIALIST IN THE NEAR EAST (HOWARD REED)
    $43,700.00;$27,545.90
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590083): TV-RADIO WORKSHOP (OMNIBUS), 1956-1957, 1955 (Reel 1032)
    TV-RADIO WORKSHOP (OMNIBUS), 1956-1957
    $6,680,000.00;$6,680,000.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590084): UNITED NATIONS ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR ASIA AND THE FAR EAST - SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF A LIBRARY, 1955 (Reel 0667)
    UNITED NATIONS ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR ASIA AND THE FAR EAST - SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF A LIBRARY
    $25,000.00;$24,838.21
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590185): PUBLICATION OF A REPORT OF A RECONNAISSANCE SURVEY OF RURAL IRAN, 1955 (Reel 0812)
    PUBLICATION OF A REPORT OF A RECONNAISSANCE SURVEY OF RURAL IRAN
    $3,550.00;$.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05590191): TO SUPPORT ATTENDANCE OF ARAB WOMEN AT SILVER JUBILEE MEETING OF INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF BUSINESS AND PROFESSIONAL WOMEN, 1955 (Reel 0760)
    TO SUPPORT ATTENDANCE OF ARAB WOMEN AT SILVER JUBILEE MEETING OF INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF BUSINESS AND PROFESSIONAL WOMEN
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05600332): FOREIGN AREA AND INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS TRAINING FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1957-58, 1956 (Reel 1040)
    FOREIGN AREA AND INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS TRAINING FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1957-58
    $1,000,000.00;$814,537.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05690021): EXPENSES INCIDENT TO VISIT TO UNITED STATES OF DR. GASTON BERGER, 1956 (Reel 0499)
    EXPENSES INCIDENT TO VISIT TO UNITED STATES OF DR. GASTON BERGER
    $5,000.00;$3,627.89
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05690106): ARAB RURAL EDUCATION SURVEY COMMISSION, 1956 January 01-1958 August 31 (Reel 0760)
    ARAB RURAL EDUCATION SURVEY COMMISSION
    $76,709.00;$76,709.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05690121): VISIT TO THE UNITED STATES BY THE MINISTER OF HEALTH, GOVERNMENT OF INDIA, 1956 (Reel 0894;3790;3896)
    VISIT TO THE UNITED STATES BY THE MINISTER OF HEALTH, GOVERNMENT OF INDIA
    $6,199.00;$6,199.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05690194): BOOKS AND FILMS ON INDIAN TEXTILE DESIGN, 1956 (Reel 0894;3822)
    BOOKS AND FILMS ON INDIAN TEXTILE DESIGN
    $2,700.00;$2,254.59
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05690320): OVERSEAS SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT TO THE GOVERNMENT OF NEPAL ON PLANNING AND DEVELOPMENT, 1956 January 01-1962 March 15 (Reel 0857)
    OVERSEAS SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT TO THE GOVERNMENT OF NEPAL ON PLANNING AND DEVELOPMENT
    $83,189.00;$83,189.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790008): PRELIMINARY ACTIVITY FOR PROPOSED URBAN PLANNING PROJECT, DELHI, INDIA, 1957 (Reel 0900)
    PRELIMINARY ACTIVITY FOR PROPOSED URBAN PLANNING PROJECT, DELHI, INDIA
    $7,200.00;$7,140.75
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790010): PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON EXAMINATION METHODS, 1957 January 01-1958 August 25 (Reel 0900)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON EXAMINATION METHODS
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790014): SEMINAR ON SECONDARY SCHOOL EDUCATION IN TURKEY, 1957 (Reel 5349;5929;5965)
    SEMINAR ON SECONDARY SCHOOL EDUCATION IN TURKEY
    $1,000.00;$842.86
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790038): PROGRAM SPECIALIST - CONSULTANT ON LABOR EDUCATION AND TRAINING, 1957 (Reel 0816)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST - CONSULTANT ON LABOR EDUCATION AND TRAINING
    $3,000.00;$1,881.17
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790083): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): TWO ADVISERS ON BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION EDUCATION, 1957 January 16-1957 April 15 (Reel 0816)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): TWO ADVISERS ON BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION EDUCATION
    $11,200.00;$8,124.07
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790087): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (PAKISTAN): CONSULTANT ON LANGUAGE TEACHING, 1957 January 24-1959 March 29 (Reel 0868;3987)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (PAKISTAN): CONSULTANT ON LANGUAGE TEACHING
    $29,482.00;$29,482.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790100): CONSULTATION WITH GADJAH MADA STATE UNIVERSITY FACULTY OF ECONOMICS (INDONESIA), 1957 (Reel 0845)
    CONSULTATION WITH GADJAH MADA STATE UNIVERSITY FACULTY OF ECONOMICS (INDONESIA)
    $13,100.00;$13,100.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790102): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS (BURMA): ADVISER ON AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1957 February 05-1959 June 30 (Reel 0830)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS (BURMA): ADVISER ON AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION AND DEVELOPMENT
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790106): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS (UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC): RURAL DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST IN SYRIA, 1957 (Reel 0790)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS AND CONSULTANTS (UNITED ARAB REPUBLIC): RURAL DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST IN SYRIA
    $75,000.00;$71,028.26
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790112): PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDONESIA): CONSULTANT, NOMMENSEN UNIVERSITY FACULTY OF ECONOMICS, 1957 (Reel 0845)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDONESIA): CONSULTANT, NOMMENSEN UNIVERSITY FACULTY OF ECONOMICS
    $5,000.00;$4,558.42
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790114): CONFERENCE ON LANGUAGE TEACHING IN PAKISTAN, 1957 (Reel 0868)
    CONFERENCE ON LANGUAGE TEACHING IN PAKISTAN
    $18,500.00;$8,550.02
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790132): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANTS ON ROBERT COLLEGE AND THE AMERICAN COLLEGE FOR GIRLS, ISTANBUL, TURKEY, 1957 (Reel 0800;5975)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANTS ON ROBERT COLLEGE AND THE AMERICAN COLLEGE FOR GIRLS, ISTANBUL, TURKEY
    $11,000.00;$10,140.23
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790135): INDUSTRIAL TRAINING OF INDIAN ENGINEERS AND SKILLED WORKERS IN THE UNITED STATES, 1957 (Reel 0901;3832;3833)
    INDUSTRIAL TRAINING OF INDIAN ENGINEERS AND SKILLED WORKERS IN THE UNITED STATES
    $15,000.00;$14,680.05
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790170): PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDONESIA): SPECIALIST ON AGRICULTURAL TRAINING AND EDUCATION, 1957 (Reel 0845)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDONESIA): SPECIALIST ON AGRICULTURAL TRAINING AND EDUCATION
    $48,000.00;$37,775.34
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790187): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDONESIA): INSTRUCTOR IN PHOTO-LITHOGRAPHY, MINISTRY OF EDUCATION PRINTING PLANT, 1957 (Reel 0845)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDONESIA): INSTRUCTOR IN PHOTO-LITHOGRAPHY, MINISTRY OF EDUCATION PRINTING PLANT
    $20,500.00;$14,472.01
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790206): PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON URBAN PLANNING, 1957 (Reel 0902)
    PROGRAM SPECIALIST (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON URBAN PLANNING
    $45,000.00;$41,342.50
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790240): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT TO THE TURKISH MINISTRY OF EDUCATION ON EXPERIMENTAL SCHOOLS, 1957 (Reel 0800;5965;5977)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT TO THE TURKISH MINISTRY OF EDUCATION ON EXPERIMENTAL SCHOOLS
    $37,291.00;$37,291.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790282): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON EDUCATION IN THE ARAB COUNTRIES, 1957 (Reel 0784)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON EDUCATION IN THE ARAB COUNTRIES
    $1,500.00;$1,500.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790288): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON REQUESTS FOR ASSISTANCE RELATIVE TO PROJECTS IN ISRAEL, 1957 (Reel 0793)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON REQUESTS FOR ASSISTANCE RELATIVE TO PROJECTS IN ISRAEL
    $5,425.00;$5,425.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790310): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON GENERAL EDUCATION, 1957 (Reel 0903)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON GENERAL EDUCATION
    $2,200.00;$1,350.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790317): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDONESIA): CONSULTATION WITH MINISTRY OF EDUCATION, INDONESIAN TEACHER TRAINING COLLEGES (PTPG'S), 1957 (Reel 0846)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDONESIA): CONSULTATION WITH MINISTRY OF EDUCATION, INDONESIAN TEACHER TRAINING COLLEGES (PTPG'S)
    $4,000.00;$2,920.65
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790349): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): SPECIALIST AND RESEARCH ASSISTANT ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1957 January 01-1962 June 30 (Reel 0903)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): SPECIALIST AND RESEARCH ASSISTANT ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT
    $78,500.00;$78,500.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790357): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON EDUCATION, 1957 (Reel 0784)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (NEAR EAST): CONSULTANT ON EDUCATION
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790358): CONSULTATION ON INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS RESEARCH IN INDIA, 1957 September 19-1959 July 20 (Reel 0903)
    CONSULTATION ON INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS RESEARCH IN INDIA
    $7,900.00;$7,900.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790359): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON EXTENSION AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT, 1957 September 20-1958 April 19 (Reel 0903)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (INDIA): CONSULTANT ON EXTENSION AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT
    $20,000.00;$16,944.24
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790360): PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (BURMA): ADVISER ON VOCATIONAL AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION, 1957 September 20-1966 August 13 (Reel 0831)
    PROGRAM SPECIALISTS (BURMA): ADVISER ON VOCATIONAL AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION
    $110,367.00;$110,367.00
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (05790361): PROGRAM SPECIALTISTS (INDIA): ADVISER ON EXTENSION TRAINING, 1957 September 20-1961 May 02 (Reel 0903;0904)
    PROGRAM SPECIALTISTS (INDIA): ADVISER ON EXTENSION TRAINING
    $92,790.00;$92,790.00